{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $15,000.00 by 2026-01-01.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $16,500.00 by 2026-02-02.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $18,000.00 by 2026-03-03.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 117, "LAW"], [126, 136, "MONEY"], [140, 150, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $19,500.00 by 2026-04-04.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $21,000.00 by 2026-05-05.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 108, "LAW"], [117, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $22,500.00 by 2026-06-06.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $24,000.00 by 2026-07-07.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 76, "CLAUSE"], [100, 111, "LAW"], [120, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $25,500.00 by 2026-08-08.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 116, "LAW"], [125, 135, "MONEY"], [139, 149, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $27,000.00 by 2026-09-09.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 120, "LAW"], [129, 139, "MONEY"], [143, 153, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $28,500.00 by 2026-10-10.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $30,000.00 by 2026-11-11.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $31,500.00 by 2026-12-12.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $33,000.00 by 2026-01-13.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 74, "CLAUSE"], [98, 126, "LAW"], [135, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $34,500.00 by 2026-02-14.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $36,000.00 by 2026-03-15.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $37,500.00 by 2026-04-16.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $39,000.00 by 2026-05-17.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $40,500.00 by 2026-06-18.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 77, "CLAUSE"], [101, 126, "LAW"], [135, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $42,000.00 by 2026-07-19.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $43,500.00 by 2026-08-20.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $45,000.00 by 2026-09-21.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $46,500.00 by 2026-10-22.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $48,000.00 by 2026-11-23.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $49,500.00 by 2026-12-24.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 114, "LAW"], [123, 133, "MONEY"], [137, 147, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $51,000.00 by 2026-01-25.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $52,500.00 by 2026-02-26.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 98, "LAW"], [107, 117, "MONEY"], [121, 131, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $54,000.00 by 2026-03-27.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $55,500.00 by 2026-04-28.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 125, "LAW"], [134, 144, "MONEY"], [148, 158, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $57,000.00 by 2026-05-01.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $58,500.00 by 2026-06-02.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 105, "LAW"], [114, 124, "MONEY"], [128, 138, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $60,000.00 by 2026-07-03.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 113, "LAW"], [122, 132, "MONEY"], [136, 146, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $61,500.00 by 2026-08-04.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 111, "LAW"], [120, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $63,000.00 by 2026-09-05.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 78, "CLAUSE"], [102, 127, "LAW"], [136, 146, "MONEY"], [150, 160, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $64,500.00 by 2026-10-06.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $66,000.00 by 2026-11-07.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 74, "CLAUSE"], [98, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $67,500.00 by 2026-12-08.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 69, "CLAUSE"], [93, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $69,000.00 by 2026-01-09.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 75, "CLAUSE"], [99, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $70,500.00 by 2026-02-10.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 116, "LAW"], [125, 135, "MONEY"], [139, 149, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $72,000.00 by 2026-03-11.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 119, "LAW"], [128, 138, "MONEY"], [142, 152, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $73,500.00 by 2026-04-12.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 101, "LAW"], [110, 120, "MONEY"], [124, 134, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $75,000.00 by 2026-05-13.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 61, "CLAUSE"], [85, 99, "LAW"], [108, 118, "MONEY"], [122, 132, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $76,500.00 by 2026-06-14.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $78,000.00 by 2026-07-15.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 116, "LAW"], [125, 135, "MONEY"], [139, 149, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $79,500.00 by 2026-08-16.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 61, "CLAUSE"], [85, 97, "LAW"], [106, 116, "MONEY"], [120, 130, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $81,000.00 by 2026-09-17.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $82,500.00 by 2026-10-18.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 108, "LAW"], [117, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $84,000.00 by 2026-11-19.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 108, "LAW"], [117, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $85,500.00 by 2026-12-20.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 77, "CLAUSE"], [101, 126, "LAW"], [135, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $87,000.00 by 2026-01-21.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $88,500.00 by 2026-02-22.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $90,000.00 by 2026-03-23.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $91,500.00 by 2026-04-24.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 79, "CLAUSE"], [103, 114, "LAW"], [123, 133, "MONEY"], [137, 147, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $93,000.00 by 2026-05-25.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 117, "LAW"], [126, 136, "MONEY"], [140, 150, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $94,500.00 by 2026-06-26.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 119, "LAW"], [128, 138, "MONEY"], [142, 152, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $96,000.00 by 2026-07-27.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 105, "LAW"], [114, 124, "MONEY"], [128, 138, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $97,500.00 by 2026-08-28.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 100, "LAW"], [109, 119, "MONEY"], [123, 133, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $99,000.00 by 2026-09-01.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $100,500.00 by 2026-10-02.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 125, "LAW"], [134, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $102,000.00 by 2026-11-03.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 102, "LAW"], [111, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $103,500.00 by 2026-12-04.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 102, "LAW"], [111, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $105,000.00 by 2026-01-05.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 109, "LAW"], [118, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $106,500.00 by 2026-02-06.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 103, "LAW"], [112, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $108,000.00 by 2026-03-07.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 117, "LAW"], [126, 137, "MONEY"], [141, 151, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $109,500.00 by 2026-04-08.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 104, "LAW"], [113, 124, "MONEY"], [128, 138, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $111,000.00 by 2026-05-09.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 108, "LAW"], [117, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $112,500.00 by 2026-06-10.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 102, "LAW"], [111, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $114,000.00 by 2026-07-11.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 76, "CLAUSE"], [100, 111, "LAW"], [120, 131, "MONEY"], [135, 145, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $115,500.00 by 2026-08-12.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 116, "LAW"], [125, 136, "MONEY"], [140, 150, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $117,000.00 by 2026-09-13.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 120, "LAW"], [129, 140, "MONEY"], [144, 154, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $118,500.00 by 2026-10-14.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 104, "LAW"], [113, 124, "MONEY"], [128, 138, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $120,000.00 by 2026-11-15.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 103, "LAW"], [112, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $121,500.00 by 2026-12-16.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 110, "LAW"], [119, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $123,000.00 by 2026-01-17.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 74, "CLAUSE"], [98, 126, "LAW"], [135, 146, "MONEY"], [150, 160, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $124,500.00 by 2026-02-18.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 102, "LAW"], [111, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $126,000.00 by 2026-03-19.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 106, "LAW"], [115, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $127,500.00 by 2026-04-20.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 110, "LAW"], [119, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $129,000.00 by 2026-05-21.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 107, "LAW"], [116, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $130,500.00 by 2026-06-22.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 77, "CLAUSE"], [101, 126, "LAW"], [135, 146, "MONEY"], [150, 160, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $132,000.00 by 2026-07-23.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 109, "LAW"], [118, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $133,500.00 by 2026-08-24.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 106, "LAW"], [115, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $135,000.00 by 2026-09-25.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 103, "LAW"], [112, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $136,500.00 by 2026-10-26.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 106, "LAW"], [115, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $138,000.00 by 2026-11-27.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 107, "LAW"], [116, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $139,500.00 by 2026-12-28.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 114, "LAW"], [123, 134, "MONEY"], [138, 148, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $141,000.00 by 2026-01-01.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 103, "LAW"], [112, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $142,500.00 by 2026-02-02.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 98, "LAW"], [107, 118, "MONEY"], [122, 132, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $144,000.00 by 2026-03-03.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 107, "LAW"], [116, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $145,500.00 by 2026-04-04.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 125, "LAW"], [134, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $147,000.00 by 2026-05-05.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 103, "LAW"], [112, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $148,500.00 by 2026-06-06.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 105, "LAW"], [114, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $15,000.00 by 2026-07-07.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 113, "LAW"], [122, 132, "MONEY"], [136, 146, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $16,500.00 by 2026-08-08.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 111, "LAW"], [120, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $18,000.00 by 2026-09-09.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 78, "CLAUSE"], [102, 127, "LAW"], [136, 146, "MONEY"], [150, 160, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $19,500.00 by 2026-10-10.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $21,000.00 by 2026-11-11.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 74, "CLAUSE"], [98, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $22,500.00 by 2026-12-12.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 69, "CLAUSE"], [93, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $24,000.00 by 2026-01-13.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 75, "CLAUSE"], [99, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $25,500.00 by 2026-02-14.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 116, "LAW"], [125, 135, "MONEY"], [139, 149, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $27,000.00 by 2026-03-15.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 119, "LAW"], [128, 138, "MONEY"], [142, 152, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $28,500.00 by 2026-04-16.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 101, "LAW"], [110, 120, "MONEY"], [124, 134, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $30,000.00 by 2026-05-17.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 61, "CLAUSE"], [85, 99, "LAW"], [108, 118, "MONEY"], [122, 132, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $31,500.00 by 2026-06-18.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $33,000.00 by 2026-07-19.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 116, "LAW"], [125, 135, "MONEY"], [139, 149, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $34,500.00 by 2026-08-20.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 61, "CLAUSE"], [85, 97, "LAW"], [106, 116, "MONEY"], [120, 130, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $36,000.00 by 2026-09-21.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $37,500.00 by 2026-10-22.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 108, "LAW"], [117, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $39,000.00 by 2026-11-23.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 108, "LAW"], [117, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $40,500.00 by 2026-12-24.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 77, "CLAUSE"], [101, 126, "LAW"], [135, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $42,000.00 by 2026-01-25.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $43,500.00 by 2026-02-26.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $45,000.00 by 2026-03-27.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $46,500.00 by 2026-04-28.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 79, "CLAUSE"], [103, 114, "LAW"], [123, 133, "MONEY"], [137, 147, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $48,000.00 by 2026-05-01.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 117, "LAW"], [126, 136, "MONEY"], [140, 150, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $49,500.00 by 2026-06-02.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 119, "LAW"], [128, 138, "MONEY"], [142, 152, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $51,000.00 by 2026-07-03.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 105, "LAW"], [114, 124, "MONEY"], [128, 138, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $52,500.00 by 2026-08-04.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 100, "LAW"], [109, 119, "MONEY"], [123, 133, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $54,000.00 by 2026-09-05.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $55,500.00 by 2026-10-06.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 125, "LAW"], [134, 144, "MONEY"], [148, 158, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $57,000.00 by 2026-11-07.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $58,500.00 by 2026-12-08.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $60,000.00 by 2026-01-09.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $61,500.00 by 2026-02-10.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $63,000.00 by 2026-03-11.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 117, "LAW"], [126, 136, "MONEY"], [140, 150, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $64,500.00 by 2026-04-12.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $66,000.00 by 2026-05-13.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 108, "LAW"], [117, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $67,500.00 by 2026-06-14.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $69,000.00 by 2026-07-15.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 76, "CLAUSE"], [100, 111, "LAW"], [120, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $70,500.00 by 2026-08-16.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 116, "LAW"], [125, 135, "MONEY"], [139, 149, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $72,000.00 by 2026-09-17.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 120, "LAW"], [129, 139, "MONEY"], [143, 153, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $73,500.00 by 2026-10-18.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $75,000.00 by 2026-11-19.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $76,500.00 by 2026-12-20.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $78,000.00 by 2026-01-21.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 74, "CLAUSE"], [98, 126, "LAW"], [135, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $79,500.00 by 2026-02-22.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $81,000.00 by 2026-03-23.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $82,500.00 by 2026-04-24.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $84,000.00 by 2026-05-25.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $85,500.00 by 2026-06-26.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 77, "CLAUSE"], [101, 126, "LAW"], [135, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $87,000.00 by 2026-07-27.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $88,500.00 by 2026-08-28.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $90,000.00 by 2026-09-01.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $91,500.00 by 2026-10-02.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $93,000.00 by 2026-11-03.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $94,500.00 by 2026-12-04.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 114, "LAW"], [123, 133, "MONEY"], [137, 147, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $96,000.00 by 2026-01-05.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $97,500.00 by 2026-02-06.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 98, "LAW"], [107, 117, "MONEY"], [121, 131, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $99,000.00 by 2026-03-07.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $100,500.00 by 2026-04-08.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 125, "LAW"], [134, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $102,000.00 by 2026-05-09.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 103, "LAW"], [112, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $103,500.00 by 2026-06-10.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 105, "LAW"], [114, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $105,000.00 by 2026-07-11.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 113, "LAW"], [122, 133, "MONEY"], [137, 147, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $106,500.00 by 2026-08-12.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 111, "LAW"], [120, 131, "MONEY"], [135, 145, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $108,000.00 by 2026-09-13.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 78, "CLAUSE"], [102, 127, "LAW"], [136, 147, "MONEY"], [151, 161, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $109,500.00 by 2026-10-14.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 109, "LAW"], [118, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $111,000.00 by 2026-11-15.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 74, "CLAUSE"], [98, 110, "LAW"], [119, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $112,500.00 by 2026-12-16.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 69, "CLAUSE"], [93, 104, "LAW"], [113, 124, "MONEY"], [128, 138, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $114,000.00 by 2026-01-17.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 75, "CLAUSE"], [99, 110, "LAW"], [119, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $115,500.00 by 2026-02-18.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 116, "LAW"], [125, 136, "MONEY"], [140, 150, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $117,000.00 by 2026-03-19.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 119, "LAW"], [128, 139, "MONEY"], [143, 153, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $118,500.00 by 2026-04-20.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 101, "LAW"], [110, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $120,000.00 by 2026-05-21.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 61, "CLAUSE"], [85, 99, "LAW"], [108, 119, "MONEY"], [123, 133, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $121,500.00 by 2026-06-22.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 102, "LAW"], [111, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $123,000.00 by 2026-07-23.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 116, "LAW"], [125, 136, "MONEY"], [140, 150, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $124,500.00 by 2026-08-24.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 61, "CLAUSE"], [85, 97, "LAW"], [106, 117, "MONEY"], [121, 131, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $126,000.00 by 2026-09-25.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 104, "LAW"], [113, 124, "MONEY"], [128, 138, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $127,500.00 by 2026-10-26.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 108, "LAW"], [117, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $129,000.00 by 2026-11-27.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 108, "LAW"], [117, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $130,500.00 by 2026-12-28.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 77, "CLAUSE"], [101, 126, "LAW"], [135, 146, "MONEY"], [150, 160, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $132,000.00 by 2026-01-01.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 110, "LAW"], [119, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $133,500.00 by 2026-02-02.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 109, "LAW"], [118, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $135,000.00 by 2026-03-03.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 107, "LAW"], [116, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $136,500.00 by 2026-04-04.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 79, "CLAUSE"], [103, 114, "LAW"], [123, 134, "MONEY"], [138, 148, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $138,000.00 by 2026-05-05.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 117, "LAW"], [126, 137, "MONEY"], [141, 151, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $139,500.00 by 2026-06-06.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 119, "LAW"], [128, 139, "MONEY"], [143, 153, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $141,000.00 by 2026-07-07.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 105, "LAW"], [114, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $142,500.00 by 2026-08-08.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 100, "LAW"], [109, 120, "MONEY"], [124, 134, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $144,000.00 by 2026-09-09.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 106, "LAW"], [115, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $145,500.00 by 2026-10-10.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 125, "LAW"], [134, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $147,000.00 by 2026-11-11.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 102, "LAW"], [111, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $148,500.00 by 2026-12-12.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 102, "LAW"], [111, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $15,000.00 by 2026-01-13.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $16,500.00 by 2026-02-14.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $18,000.00 by 2026-03-15.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 117, "LAW"], [126, 136, "MONEY"], [140, 150, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $19,500.00 by 2026-04-16.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $21,000.00 by 2026-05-17.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 108, "LAW"], [117, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $22,500.00 by 2026-06-18.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $24,000.00 by 2026-07-19.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 76, "CLAUSE"], [100, 111, "LAW"], [120, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $25,500.00 by 2026-08-20.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 116, "LAW"], [125, 135, "MONEY"], [139, 149, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $27,000.00 by 2026-09-21.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 120, "LAW"], [129, 139, "MONEY"], [143, 153, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $28,500.00 by 2026-10-22.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $30,000.00 by 2026-11-23.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $31,500.00 by 2026-12-24.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $33,000.00 by 2026-01-25.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 74, "CLAUSE"], [98, 126, "LAW"], [135, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $34,500.00 by 2026-02-26.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $36,000.00 by 2026-03-27.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $37,500.00 by 2026-04-28.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $39,000.00 by 2026-05-01.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $40,500.00 by 2026-06-02.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 77, "CLAUSE"], [101, 126, "LAW"], [135, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $42,000.00 by 2026-07-03.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $43,500.00 by 2026-08-04.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $45,000.00 by 2026-09-05.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $46,500.00 by 2026-10-06.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $48,000.00 by 2026-11-07.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $49,500.00 by 2026-12-08.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 114, "LAW"], [123, 133, "MONEY"], [137, 147, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $51,000.00 by 2026-01-09.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $52,500.00 by 2026-02-10.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 98, "LAW"], [107, 117, "MONEY"], [121, 131, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $54,000.00 by 2026-03-11.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $55,500.00 by 2026-04-12.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 125, "LAW"], [134, 144, "MONEY"], [148, 158, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $57,000.00 by 2026-05-13.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 103, "LAW"], [112, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $58,500.00 by 2026-06-14.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 105, "LAW"], [114, 124, "MONEY"], [128, 138, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $60,000.00 by 2026-07-15.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 113, "LAW"], [122, 132, "MONEY"], [136, 146, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $61,500.00 by 2026-08-16.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 68, "CLAUSE"], [92, 111, "LAW"], [120, 130, "MONEY"], [134, 144, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $63,000.00 by 2026-09-17.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 78, "CLAUSE"], [102, 127, "LAW"], [136, 146, "MONEY"], [150, 160, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $64,500.00 by 2026-10-18.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $66,000.00 by 2026-11-19.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 74, "CLAUSE"], [98, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $67,500.00 by 2026-12-20.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 69, "CLAUSE"], [93, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $69,000.00 by 2026-01-21.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 75, "CLAUSE"], [99, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $70,500.00 by 2026-02-22.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 71, "CLAUSE"], [95, 116, "LAW"], [125, 135, "MONEY"], [139, 149, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $72,000.00 by 2026-03-23.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 119, "LAW"], [128, 138, "MONEY"], [142, 152, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $73,500.00 by 2026-04-24.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 101, "LAW"], [110, 120, "MONEY"], [124, 134, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sara Alvarez confirmed FirstBank would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $75,000.00 by 2026-05-25.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "ORG"], [48, 61, "CLAUSE"], [85, 99, "LAW"], [108, 118, "MONEY"], [122, 132, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "John Doe confirmed GlobalTrust would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $76,500.00 by 2026-06-26.", "entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [19, 30, "ORG"], [46, 63, "CLAUSE"], [87, 102, "LAW"], [111, 121, "MONEY"], [125, 135, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Emily Park confirmed Acme Corp would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $78,000.00 by 2026-07-27.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 30, "ORG"], [46, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 116, "LAW"], [125, 135, "MONEY"], [139, 149, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "David Kim confirmed BrightWare would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $79,500.00 by 2026-08-28.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 30, "ORG"], [46, 61, "CLAUSE"], [85, 97, "LAW"], [106, 116, "MONEY"], [120, 130, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Mina Patel confirmed Nova Advisors would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $81,000.00 by 2026-09-01.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 104, "LAW"], [113, 123, "MONEY"], [127, 137, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Robert King confirmed Lumen LLC would meet the termination clause in accordance with the Data Protection Act and pay $82,500.00 by 2026-10-02.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 31, "ORG"], [47, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 108, "LAW"], [117, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Anna Chen confirmed Vertex Holdings would meet the payment clause in accordance with the Consumer Rights Act and pay $84,000.00 by 2026-11-03.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 35, "ORG"], [51, 65, "CLAUSE"], [89, 108, "LAW"], [117, 127, "MONEY"], [131, 141, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michael Smith confirmed Mercury Finance would meet the confidentiality clause in accordance with the Intellectual Property Act and pay $85,500.00 by 2026-12-04.", "entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [24, 39, "ORG"], [55, 77, "CLAUSE"], [101, 126, "LAW"], [135, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Lucas Wright confirmed Crestview LLC would meet the governing law clause in accordance with the Employment Law and pay $87,000.00 by 2026-01-05.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 110, "LAW"], [119, 129, "MONEY"], [133, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Nina Rivera confirmed Skyline Group would meet the indemnification clause in accordance with the Contract Act and pay $88,500.00 by 2026-02-06.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 35, "ORG"], [51, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 109, "LAW"], [118, 128, "MONEY"], [132, 142, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Daniel Clark confirmed Prime Capital would meet the force majeure clause in accordance with the Privacy Act and pay $90,000.00 by 2026-03-07.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 107, "LAW"], [116, 126, "MONEY"], [130, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Olivia Reed confirmed Everest Holdings would meet the dispute resolution clause in accordance with the Company Law and pay $91,500.00 by 2026-04-08.", "entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [22, 38, "ORG"], [54, 79, "CLAUSE"], [103, 114, "LAW"], [123, 133, "MONEY"], [137, 147, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Carlos Ortiz confirmed Atlantic Partners would meet the liability clause in accordance with the Financial Regulations and pay $93,000.00 by 2026-05-09.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 40, "ORG"], [56, 72, "CLAUSE"], [96, 117, "LAW"], [126, 136, "MONEY"], [140, 150, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Michelle Young confirmed Blue Ridge would meet the deliverables clause in accordance with the Anti-Money Laundering Act and pay $94,500.00 by 2026-06-10.", "entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [25, 35, "ORG"], [51, 70, "CLAUSE"], [94, 119, "LAW"], [128, 138, "MONEY"], [142, 152, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ethan Turner confirmed NorthStar LLC would meet the scope clause in accordance with the Trade Secrets Act and pay $96,000.00 by 2026-07-11.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 36, "ORG"], [52, 64, "CLAUSE"], [88, 105, "LAW"], [114, 124, "MONEY"], [128, 138, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Sophia Grant confirmed Silverline would meet the notice clause in accordance with the Insolvency Act and pay $97,500.00 by 2026-08-12.", "entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [23, 33, "ORG"], [49, 62, "CLAUSE"], [86, 100, "LAW"], [109, 119, "MONEY"], [123, 133, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Liam Evans confirmed Summit Equity would meet the assignment clause in accordance with the Competition Act and pay $99,000.00 by 2026-09-13.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 34, "ORG"], [50, 67, "CLAUSE"], [91, 106, "LAW"], [115, 125, "MONEY"], [129, 139, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Isabella Brooks confirmed Pioneer Trust would meet the arbitration clause in accordance with the Environmental Protection Act and pay $100,500.00 by 2026-10-14.", "entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [26, 39, "ORG"], [55, 73, "CLAUSE"], [97, 125, "LAW"], [134, 145, "MONEY"], [149, 159, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Noah Lewis confirmed Apex Financial would meet the warranty clause in accordance with the Taxation Act and pay $102,000.00 by 2026-11-15.", "entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [21, 35, "ORG"], [51, 66, "CLAUSE"], [90, 102, "LAW"], [111, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
{"text": "Ava Scott confirmed Zenith Group would meet the audit clause in accordance with the Banking Regulation and pay $103,500.00 by 2026-12-16.", "entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [20, 32, "ORG"], [48, 60, "CLAUSE"], [84, 102, "LAW"], [111, 122, "MONEY"], [126, 136, "DATE"]]}
